=Love Start From Marriage= =Episode 10=
= الحب يبدأ من الزواج = = الحلقة 10 =
Susu, are you saying that
سوسو ، هل تقول ذلك
Xia Qiange took place of Xia Qianxun and married Mr. Gu?
استغرق شيا Qiange مكان شيا Qianxun وتزوج السيد قو؟
Susu,
لبن،
you need to show some proof to convince us.
تحتاج إلى إظهار بعض الأدلة لإقناعنا.
You're Qiange, not Qianxun.
أنت Qiange ، وليس Qianxun.
Just confess to Mr. Gu.
فقط اعترف للسيد جو.
He's your elder sister's husband after all.
إنه زوج أختك الكبرى بعد كل شيء.
I'm sure he'll forgive you.
أنا متأكد من أنه سوف يغفر لك.
Miss Su.
ملكة جمال سو.
If you can't provide any proof,
إذا لم تتمكن من تقديم أي دليل ،
I have no choice but send you to the police.
ليس لدي خيار سوى إرسالك إلى الشرطة.
Qiange, say something.
Qiange ، قولي شيئًا.
I'm looking out for you.
أنا أبحث عنك.
Stop making it worse.
توقف عن جعله أسوأ.
What proof do you have?
ما الدليل لديك؟
Last time, I saw
آخر مرة رأيت
you still using the phone shell that I gave you as a gift.
ما زلت تستخدم غلاف الهاتف الذي قدمته لك كهدية.
You're still using it.
ما زلت تستخدمه.
That's so moving.
هذا مؤثر جدا.
(How could I miss that?)
(كيف يمكنني أن أفوت ذلك؟)
Why are you holding my phone?
لماذا تمسك هاتفي؟
The phone shell belonged to my sister Qiange.
قذيفة الهاتف تخص أختي Qiange.
But she gave it to me.
لكنها أعطته لي.
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
However,
لكن،
fingerprints don't lie, am I right?
بصمات الأصابع لا تكذب ، هل أنا على حق؟
Qiange?
Qiange؟
Mr. Gu.
السيد.  قو.
Marital fraud is a big deal.
الاحتيال الزوجي هو صفقة كبيرة.
Maybe we should clear the air.
ربما يجب علينا تنقية الهواء.
Xia Qianxun can unlock the phone of Xia Qiange.
يمكن لـ Xia Qianxun فتح هاتف Xia Qiange.
Mrs. Gu got some explaining to do.
حصلت السيدة جو على بعض الشرح لتفعله.
This is always the phone of Xia Qianxun's, mine.
هذا دائمًا هاتف Xia Qianxun الخاص بي.
I can unlock it for sure.
يمكنني فتحه بالتأكيد.
(Still resisting?)
(مازلت تقاوم؟)
(Calling Xia Qiange...)
(استدعاء Xia Qiange ...)
What?
ماذا؟
Did you, Miss Susu, think that
هل تعتقد ذلك يا آنسة سوسو
by stealing my phone
بسرقة هاتفي
you're good to frame me?
هل انت جيد لتأطير لي؟
Dear.
عزيزي.
Please call me at my number
من فضلك اتصل بي على رقمي
so that they can give up framing.
حتى يتمكنوا من التخلي عن التأطير.
(Calling Xia Qianxun...)
(استدعاء Xia Qianxun ...)
(A call from Gu Chengze)
(مكالمة من Gu Chengze)
Your elder sister's phone has been decoded.
تم فك تشفير هاتف أختك الكبرى.
Use it.
استخدمه.
That's not possible.
هذا غير ممكن.
You must have done some work on it!
لابد أنك قمت ببعض العمل على ذلك!
Enough!
كافية!
Who do you think you are?
من تظن نفسك؟
I'll teach you a lesson if you keep tangling us.
سأعلمك درسا إذا واصلت التشابك بيننا.
And you, Jin Sula.
وأنت جين سولا.
Do what you should've been doing.
افعل ما كان يجب أن تفعله.
Or,
أو،
I'll promise the Gu's won't hire you anymore.
سوف أعدك بأن Gu's لن يوظفك بعد الآن.
Is this what you've got?
هل هذا ما لديك؟
(Why did Xia Qiange not answer the phone?)
(لماذا لم يرد Xia Qiange على الهاتف؟)
(Calling Xia Qiange...)
(استدعاء Xia Qiange ...)
(Qianxun after marriage does look weird.)
(يبدو Qianxun بعد الزواج غريبًا.)
By the way,
على فكرة،
I haven't met your twin sister yet.
لم أقابل أختك التوأم بعد.
She didn't attend our wedding.
لم تحضر حفل زفافنا.
Are you also suspicious of me?
هل أنت أيضا تشك بي؟
No. Just asking.
لا انا فقط اسأل.
You can come and work at the Gu's next week.
يمكنك المجيء والعمل في Gu's الأسبوع المقبل.
Everything has been set ready for you.
تم إعداد كل شيء من أجلك.
Okay.
تمام.